<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<demos><!--This is an autogenerated file, please do not modify-->
   <name>Cupid</name>
   <type>toolbox</type>
   <icon>HelpIcon.DEMOS</icon>
   <website/>
   <description>Useful for computations with more than 40 standard univariate probability distributions. In addition, other distributions can be derived from these by mathematical transformations (e.g., inverse, exponential, power, or log), by truncation, probability mixing, convolution, or taking order statistics. The object-oriented framework allows composition of transformations (e.g., the distribution of the square-root of X, where X is a probability mixture formed from two truncated distributions). For any of its distributions, Cupid can compute standard quantities such as the density and cumulative density functions, mean, variance, skewness, kurtosis, percentiles, etc. It can also estimate distribution parameter values (e.g., by maximum likelihood, minimum chi-square, probit analysis), even when certain parameters are fixed or constrainted, possibly with constraints across multiple distributions. Finally, it can generate random numbers and tthere is some support for multivariate random number generation.</description>
   <demosection>
      <label>Cupid</label>
      <demoitem>
         <label>DemoCupid1</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>DemoCupid1</source>
         <file>html/DemoCupid1.html</file>
      </demoitem>
      <demoitem>
         <label>DemoFitConstrained</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>DemoFitConstrained</source>
         <file>html/DemoFitConstrained.html</file>
      </demoitem>
      <demoitem>
         <label>DemoLogPearsonIII</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>DemoLogPearsonIII</source>
         <file>html/DemoLogPearsonIII.html</file>
      </demoitem>
      <demoitem>
         <label>DemoMLSE</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>DemoMLSE</source>
         <file>html/DemoMLSE.html</file>
      </demoitem>
      <demoitem>
         <label>DemoProbit</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>DemoProbit</source>
         <file>html/DemoProbit.html</file>
      </demoitem>
      <demoitem>
         <label>DemoRandGen</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>DemoRandGen</source>
         <file>html/DemoRandGen.html</file>
      </demoitem>
      <demoitem>
         <label>Demo_dMATLAB</label>
         <type>other</type>
         <source>Demo_dMATLAB</source>
         <file>html/Demo_dMATLAB.html</file>
      </demoitem>
   </demosection>
</demos>